BGM
Here we go, Amechare, this time an interview with a homebrewer!
So, of course, our guest is that very famous person!
Please come in!
Yes, I'm Yuzuki Ichikawa. Please give my best regards to you.
Pretty for you
I'm a brand new me
Hear me
me
Hear me me me
Yumi-yes, that's right, today I'd like to get to know you a little bit better, so I'd like to introduce myself as Yuzucha, a recent customer of yours.
I'm a brand new me Hear me me me me me me me
I'm sure you're so busy that you don't have time to sleep, but what made you decide to become an idol in the first place?
Ever since I was in kindergarten, my dreams for the future were either to become a mermaid princess or an idol.
It's quite surprising that you want to be a mermaid.
She has such a beautiful face... and this... and this... and this... and this... and this... and this... and why is she so beautiful?
How can someone so beautiful exist in this world? I've always been in love at first sight.
I was trying to decide which one I wanted to be when my friend told me that the Little Mermaid doesn't exist in this world.
When I realized that I couldn't be a mermaid anymore, I decided to be an idol.
I've always wanted to be an idol, but then a friend of mine who is like a big sister to me told me to try out for Stardust's Shidemaru-kun.
I see... I see... So now let me continue...
What do you think of your position in the group?
When AmeFlashy was first formed, I was really worried about my position.
There was a day when I had a strategy meeting to figure out where I wanted to be in the group.
I used to work in a large group, so I didn't have a microphone or anything, and I didn't talk much.
I thought this would be my chance to speak, so I tried to be more active in speaking, but for some reason I didn't get selected for the MC contest.
Well, I was aiming for the MC position, but Kojima was chosen as the MC, so I thought, "Well, what should I do?
So when I thought about what to do...
But I thought that if Yuzu was there
I thought that if Yuzu was there, the atmosphere would be more cheerful, or to put it another way, the group would be more cheerful if Yuzu was in a position to provide mental care.
I thought that there were not many girls who could play such a role, so I thought it would be easy to say that I was a mental caregiver.
I thought it would be easier to say that I do mental care, and I'm currently doing mental care for self-inflicted amebiasis.
I see. So that's what you're thinking about. I'm sure you must be really busy every day.
What do you do on your days off?
Well, I'm pretty evolved. Basically, I don't go out much from morning till noon.I don't usually go out in the morning or afternoon.
When I hang out with my friends, we usually have dinner in the evening and go out for dinner in the evening.
When I have fun with friends, I usually have dinner with them in the evening, and then we go out for dinner in the evening.
My activities are basically animal-like, and I tend to spend most of my time in the evening and night.
So when we talk about going to Disney, I really like to go to Japan in the evening.
I've heard some rumors about you.
By the way, I heard a rumor that you have a pet you want to buy.
Can you tell me which pet it is? I'm really interested in buying a cute, pure-white, wide-eyed pet named Pellet.
It's super cute, but I heard that it's very vicious.
It says that they can be kept by humans, but they're carnivores.
I want to buy one, but they don't exist, so if I could buy one, I'd want to buy an Eevee.
I'd like to buy all of them if they were super cute and fluffy Pokémon.
But I'm a little scared of egg-shaped Pokémon, because if they really existed, I'd be surprised.
But Eevee is like a Pitcher.
But Eevee is so cute, I want to play "Char" with it!
I think it would be a nice dream to buy an Eevee, wouldn't it? I'd like to buy one too.
By the way, do you have any dreams as an Eevee?
I'd like to go and live in the countryside with my grandma and the four of us.
Because we're more than family, we can say what we want to say, and it's easy to be together.
That's why I don't feel like I have to go out of my way for anything anymore.
Because we understand each other's personalities, and because we're the four of us who met here.
I don't want to destroy it, and even if I become a grandmother, we'll live the same life, smiling and eating watermelon.
I might want to live a quiet, happy, peaceful life, ringing wind chimes and all.
I felt a little closer to the winners, and it was a lot of fun.
I know I'm busy at times, but please come visit me again if you like.
That's all for today's guest, Ms. Izumi Ichikawa!
Thank you very much!